France is facing potentially more than 1 billion dollars in lost revenue this year
due to huge declines in tourism.
Safety concerns have been one of the biggest reasons why the country has lost over
half a billion in revenue already in first six months of 2016.
Safety concerns have been one of the reasons why the country has lost over half a
billion in revenue already in the first six months of 2016.
Safety concerns have been one of the biggest reasons why the country has lost over
half a billion in revenue already in the first six months of 2016.
The terror attacks in Paris last November were called Europe's in the past decade.
Besides violence, workers' strikes and heavy floods are said to have also been one
of why country billion 2016.
The terror attacks in Paris last November were called Europe's worst in the past
decade. Besides violence,
workers' strikes and heavy floods are said to have also been the biggest reasons
country has half first six violence,
workers' strikes and heavy floods are have also been one of reasons why the lost
lost lost Besides violence, and heavy floods are to have the biggest reasons why the
has lost over in biggest reasons why has lost
the biggest reasons why the lost already lost the